One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Zoro vs. Kaku
Oni Giri!
Whoa! Damn that giraffe and Moss Head!
Are they trying to destroy this tower?
This is...
Gates of Justice
Underground Passage
the Gates of Justice?
So I can get there by following this?
Gates of Justice
Underground Passage
I hope Nami-san and the others are
already headed to Robin-chan by now.
I also need to hurry and get this No. 1 key to her.
I'd better get going!
You bitch! Come on already!
We're finally on the Bridge of Hesitation!
Look, Nico Robin!
You can see the opened
Gates of Justice, can't you?
It took a long time. It really took a long time.
But I'm finally here.
Once I've gone through those gates,
I'll be the government's...
No, the world's hero!
The bridge that continues onto the other
side of the gates is indeed rising up.
It now awaits the hero's crossing!
This is wonderful! Just take a look
at the path to my bright future!
Well, for you, I guess it's the path to hell, huh?
Right? You think so too, right, Nico Robin?
– No!
– Hey, what're you doing?!
Ow!
Hey! Stop!
You... That's enough already, you bitch!
You still don't get it?!
It's pointless to try and struggle!
Luffy.
Everyone.
Everyone!
Gotta hurry! Gotta hurry!
It'll be meaningless if I
can't make it in time! Hm?
I can see something up ahead!
We'll reach our destination
in about ten minutes!
Hurry and check the ships' formation!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Stand up already, you bitch!
Now, let's go, Nico Robin!
Is this the exit?!
You... Straw Hat!
Ah! Franky!
What're you doing here, you jerk?!
You idiot! Enough with the attitude already!
I'm on your side right now! Just give it up!
Lucci, huh? So you're having
a tough time against him?
Where's Nico Robin? I brought two keys.
Shall I give you a hand?
No. More importantly,
please stop Robin.
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through the doors behind the pigeon guy.
Robin has already been taken away.
I'll restrain him.
Just super leave it to me, you jerk!
I'm saying that if I had to choose,
I like meat better!
And I'm saying it doesn't matter, herbivore!
Hm?
In any case, I'll go ahead and take your key.
If I can't make it in time,
it'll be the same as defeat.
Two-Sword Style: Nigiri...
Do you get stronger when you
wear a bandana on your head?
Who knows?
Toro!
Otoro!
Hirameki!
Samon!
Jumping causes blind spots.
Giraffe Scythe!
Iron Body: Safe
What?!
I'm secure in my square safe.
Shut up! What the hell are you doing?!
You're so naive.
Have you not noticed?
What?
Giraffes have four legs.
Tempest Kick!
Like I said, are you gonna fight or not?!
Where are you looking?
My attack has already started.
The slash attacks I directed upwards...
will deflect off the ceiling...
and pour down on you!
Giraffe Cloudburst!
Iron Body.
Slashing pellets...
Dammit! I can't block them!
Nose Pistol!
You bastard!
What a tough guy you are.
I'm flabbergasted.
I've trained my body, you damn gi-riff-raff!
Gi-riff-raff? I am a giraffe!
Gi-riff-raff.
That's wrong! I'm not gi-riff-raff!
– Shut up!
– Hm?
Gi-riff-raff... Gi-riff-raff...
Stop rambling. I couldn't care less!
If you're mocking me, you'll pay for it.
Likewise. You'd better prepare yourself.
Playtime is over.
First, I'm gonna break through that Iron Body!
One-Sword Style:
Draw...
Lion Song!
Tempest Kick!
Dragon Cleave!
Would you have cut me if I were iron?!
It's my call as to whether I use
Iron Body to block your attack.
I see. I guess it's not that simple, huh?
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Now, bring it on!
Three-Sword Style...
A strength contest this time?
How interesting.
Nose Pistol!
Nigori Zake!
What strength!
You speak so damn pompously.
You're the type who can't even
imagine your own fall, aren't you?
Humble yourself!
You too!
Rubber Rubber...
Gatling!
Paper Art.
Rubber Rubber...
Pistol!
Shave!
Straw Hat!
Tsk!
Tempest Kick!
Weapons Left!
Shave!
What?!
Rubber Rubber...
Rocket!
What?!
Rubber Rubber...
Bazooka!
I still haven't shown you...
a wild giraffe's true potential!
Stop talking! Just show it to me.
Sure thing!
Have a good look at the giraffe's power!
Giraffe Gun Battery!
There's no giraffe like that.
Ultimate Nose Pistol:
Giraffe Turret Strike!
It stretched?!
See? What'd I tell you?
That long neck is vulnerable.
That's not totally true.
Tempest Kick:
White Drill!
You're more exposed.
Tsk! Just what kind of creature is he?!
I won't miss next time.
Giraffe Gun Battery!
Wha-
Oh, shoot! I pulled my neck in so far that my limbs extended!
How the hell does your body work anyway?!
It's as if flour got crammed in
and got pushed out as noodles.
Just like a pasta machine!
Pasta Machine!
You just made up that attack!
I like my long neck, but long arms and legs have their advantages, too.
I'm an expert fighter who turns
unexpected situations into opportunities.
Just watch my technique
using this long reach!
Giraffe Turret Strike!
You couldn't come up with a new attack?!
Enough is enough!
Three-Sword Style:
Dragon Twister!
Iron Body!
How powerful!
Shave!
Moon Walk!
He jumped into the upper floor!
Pasta Machine!
I've kept you waiting!
My arms, legs, and neck...
If I can control their reach at will,
my swordplay will be uncontested!
I employ the Four-Sword Style.
I can now make full use of the giraffe's power!
You no longer have any chance against me!
The giraffe is quite powerful.
You can retract that neck to avoid its handicap.
You use the Four-Sword Style.
Hmph!
What?!
He stayed my swords?!
None of those things establish that you can defeat me.
Three-Sword Style:
Spinning...
Leopard...
He's gonna fly towards me!
Balls!
Paper Art!
Impossible! I'm sure I saw through his attack!
Don't tell me...
he actually anticipated my reaction?!
What are you so surprised about?
Don't tell me you've never been cut before.
Hmph! Well, well. It looks like you weren't just full of hot air.
I underestimated you a bit. But no longer.
I've mastered the Six Powers. On top of that,
I now have the wild powers of a giraffe.
Technique, power, or speed...
You couldn't possibly beat me in any way!
You won't have another opening to attack!
Tempest Kick: Shuriken!
Giraffe Turret Strike!
Dammit!
My neck is like a whip.
Giraffe Whip!
And now to speed it up!
Fierce Giraffe!
How's this?! Where's your swagger now?!
The four-sword attacks will
not stop. Surrender!
Giraffe Fury!
Here I come!
What a savage assault!
Well, well! What's the matter?!
All you can do now is block!
You can't defeat me!
You're mere pirates.
It was a mistake to go up against the
World Government in the first place!
Now that it's come to this, you must die in the name of justice!
Just like that woman!
You son of a bitch!
What was that?!
For a moment, he appeared as a demon with three faces and six arms!
What the hell is with this guy?!
You got cocky.
You said too much.
You're tired of listening to me?
Then I'll use my strongest
Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
the one that slashed this tower...
and end this battle by splitting you in two!
Give it up. You have nowhere to escape.
It's on a completely different level from
the demonstration I gave earlier!
Idiot!
You're the one who should give up.
Demonic Nine-Sword Style:
Asura!
The demon I saw earlier!
His spirit manifests as such a powerful illusion?!
Splendid! But it's too late!
You're the one who's too late.
Dodge this Tempest Kick before making such a boast!
Sky Slicer!
My slash attack...
turned into mist?!
I welcome pain and suffering.
I chose a life of constant struggle!
Asura: Silver Mist!
I've got...
a message for you from
the junior boss of Galley-La.
When you see those guys, tell them...
He said you're all fired.
Paulie, huh?
I see. That's too bad.
I'm not really cut out for much other than being an assassin.
You could still work in a zoo.
Hey, be nice.
Sorry.
Hm?
Hey, Moss Head! Where's the key?!
Yeah.
I just got it.
I see.
It looks like you guys really put on a show.
Didn't you guys cause the tower
to slip even more? Is it okay?
Who cares? That's not important.
Anyway, we now have all the keys.
Yeah.
Let's hurry to Robin.
Run!
Just run! Open that throttle, boys!
We've gotta survive so we don't worry our Bro and the Straw Hats!
Ribbit!
Run for your lives! I don't care if it breaks your legs!
Yeah!
Run!
We're counting on you, giants!
You guys, if you're just gonna ride,
then at least be quiet!
Yeah, I agree!
Go! In the name of Elbaf!
Shut up!
Grandma! Hurry! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hey, Chimney! I'm old! Show a little kindness!
Seriously, I can't keep running
unless I refuel myself.
Whoa!
Grandma! He's gonna fall off!
Pull him up! Pull him up!
Boy, you sure are demanding, geez!
Grandma!
"Hurry up," right? I know!
The bridge is finally complete!
I can't stop laughing!
Hey! Guards at the Gates of Justice!
Are you guys ready?!
Yes, sir! The escort ship is already
in front of the third column and...
That's not it! Why aren't you
coming out to salute me?!
The hero Spandam the Great is passing through!
Ah! Y-Yes! We'll be right out!
Geez, those idiots!
They can't do anything on their own!
Hey, Nico Robin. Look at that.
That small gate is the actual entrance.
When you pass through it, you'll cross
the border between heaven and hell.
And that's the moment my name
will be engraved in history!
Oops. Where're you trying to run away to now?
I'm actually sympathizing with you, at least.
But what can we do about it?
Your life is worthless.
Hurry up and die.
That bitch!
I don't wanna die.
I don't wanna die!
I can't die!
I've had enough, you bitch!
Stand up already and...
What? She isn't moving. What's going on?!
She's biting into the stone bridge!
She just doesn't know when
to give up! How irritating!
It's detestable how she clings to life!
It's pitiful and vulgar!
You're a criminal! The only way you
can make others happy is by dying!
Why must you act so miserable
until the very last moment?!
I fear death so much.
I don't wanna die!
Help me, everyone!
Luffy!
Finger Pistol!
I told you that doesn't work...!
Yellow Lotus!
Straw Hat!
No!
My mission is to get through those
doors as soon as possible!
It's no use. You shall not pass.
Shut up!
Strong...
Iron Body.
Hammer!
What? He doesn't budge an inch.
It was strong enough to blow Chapapa away.
I see. You defeated Fukuro before coming here.
Unfortunately for you, my power level
is five times higher than his.
I'm impressed that you were able to defeat Fukuro.
I can say that you're already
within the realm of superhumans.
As I suspected, he's an order of magnitude
stronger than the others.
However, now you die.
Rubber Rubber...
Jet Pistol!
What the hell did you do?!
What's that steam?!
Gear Second.
This doesn't last too long.
But I'll stop him, so you go on ahead, Franky!
Robin's waiting!
Okay, Straw Hat!
I don't know what's going on,
but finish him off with that!
I said I wouldn't let you do that...
didn't I?
Whoa! So you have powers too?!
First, I'll kill you, Franky.
Jet Whip!
Did you forget, Straw Hat Luffy?
At Galley-La, you went down
with a single blow from this form.
Oh, that? I just needed some meat.
Shave!
Finger Pistol!
Rubber Rubber...
Iron Body!
Jet Bazooka!
Franky!
Please save Robin!
You bitch! You still don't get it?!
I said this is useless!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
There's no hope left for you!
I'm not going anywhere!
I'm sure they're all coming to rescue me!
Super leave it to me!